[Music]
DJ Jake Alex, I come from Paris to see
you. Yeah. Yeah. Can we take a photo? We
come all the way from What's going on,
guys? Bro, I'm following like crazy,
bro. I never thought I'm going to meet
you, bro. Nice to meet you, man.
Appreciate, bro. See you. See you. Take
care, brother.
That's the most random. I was scared,
bro. I'm like, what the [__] is going
on? Oh [__] that was funny. We're on
our way right now to go pick up my SVJ
and go see the Bugatti. If you guys
don't know, yes, the Bugatti has been
crashed. Uh, I'm going to try and
disclose as much information as I can.
We are currently right now in the
process of figuring out what's gonna
happen with it. If it's going to be a
total loss or if I'm gonna stay with it.
So, figuring out the repairs, how much
time, you know, I don't really want to
talk about the Bugatti much cuz I got a
brand new [__] SVJ and I just got it
tuned with a flame map and I want to see
what that's all about. It's my first
time having one. It's the lowest mild
SVJ in the nation roadster. So, it had
500 miles when I got it. I don't even
want to know how many it has now. But
let's just say that the miles from this
point forward, they're going to be very
very very well.
[Music]
Honestly, I I like it better. I'm not
going to lie. Me, too. Honestly, it's I
think this is the car that fits you the
best, right? I feel like I I skipped the
level. I went pista SV Bugatti. Like I I
kind of left something in between and uh
I guess that had to happen for me to get
this. Let's give a warm welcome to my
brand new Lamborghini SVJ
set and forget edition roadster
roadster. Can't forget that. That was an
extra 200 grand, right? That that that
hurt my pocket.
[__] All right. So, this car is a
little filthy right now. Little filthy
right now. So, we just finished wrapping
it, finished doing the wheels, and
obviously our beautiful set and forget.
I feel like everybody that gets an SVJ,
it's like super basic. They all look the
same. And what better place to place
that set and forget than in the SVJ
logo. I put it under the wing of all the
Bugattis. I put it on the Porsche on the
Lambo that caught fire and I couldn't
figure out a place where it looked cool
here. So, I decided to put it there.
It's my first Roadster in a while. Very
excited for it. It's about due time that
you had a convertible. Yeah. Yeah. We
almost had a convertible happen over
there, but thank god that didn't happen,
but we would have been [__] So,
before that, this is David. And you guys
know who David is. Nice to meet you. So,
David didn't look like this like 3 days
ago. So David has been living with me
for the last month. Month already. Damn.
Time flies. Yeah. I can't believe that.
It's a completely different man, bro.
Look at that. That's a couple days
after. That's a couple long nights. This
is the same thing. It's he has to remind
me every single day of that dude. Every
single day. Why? Why? You know why? Come
on, man. I don't know why. So David has
been living with me for the last month.
I've been helping him take 1,000 to
100,000. Right now it is currently 7:22.
That's counting on 9,300. Right now
we're at $9,300.
So, we've taken all of these trades.
We've blown it one time and he's
learning the journey. He's kind of like
my like like a guinea pig. Yeah, he's
your guinea pig. Yeah, he's a big
[__] guinea pig, bro. He looks like
one, too. No. Yeah. No, now he does.
Yeah. So, he's been learning how to
trade with me. We've been scaling the
account. And if I successfully do this
with him, I'm going to teach other
people how to do it. So, he's been kind
of riding with me basically everywhere
and anywhere we go. Next week, we're
going to drop week three of us taking
the,000 to 100,000. So, make sure you
guys check that out. Luckily, he was not
in the car when this happened. Yeah, I
was up there cuz if he was, I think we
would have actually like had a had a
problem, right? So, the car would have
stopped us with all the extra weight.
So, obviously this is a very unfortunate
situation. My one of 60 Bugatti Chiron
Pure Sports in the world. No longer
going to probably be with us. So, she
was obviously involved in an accident.
Um, we're all good. I'm good. Seas was
good. He was in the car and the person
that was involved in it was good. No,
nothing happened to anybody. Thank God.
Which is the important part. Hey, how
about you leave that alone, my brother?
You said what? Stop breaking the Bugatti
more, bro. Yeah, man. What the [__]
dude? There's You cannot break it more.
Clearly. You want to bet? You want to
bet? I don't want to back. I don't even
know. Yeah, obviously it was a very
unfortunate situation. Prices have gone
up now. Now there's only 59 in the
world. Thanks, bro. Now, now how am I
supposed to get one? You know how hard
it is already for to get one? And then
on top of that, now there's one less.
You know how bad this sucks, bro? You
know how bad it sucks to have to
continuously pay $70,000 a month for a
car that you can't drive, you can't even
look at, and that you probably might
take a [__] fat out on. Welcome to
the day in the life of Alex G. Oh, nice.
Yeah. So, right here, Seas, at the
moment, he was not wearing his seat belt
and his head, look at it, right here,
flew and crashed right into that right
there. Thank god I have a hard head.
It's a It's a joke. That obviously did
not happen. That's why you always got to
wear your seat belt. Always. Yeah. Yeah.
Thank God. I mean, everybody's wearing
their seatelt. There's nothing more
gangster than wearing your seatelt. You
know who said the ice cube said that
about Tupac? He didn't know anybody more
gangster than Tupac. And Tupac wore his
seatelt everywhere he went. Tupac was
one of the biggest thugs I know. And he
always was.
I don't even know. I can't even get in.
There you go. Actually, how do you
drive? I can drive this with my knee.
How tall are you?
Remember, that's a secret. Remember, if
I'm 69, you know what I'm saying? If I'm
6'2, you're [__] like seven feet. 69.
69. 69. Sorry for you 69 people. This is
what you're gonna look like. Yeah.
Honestly, this [__] sucks, bro. That guy
I obviously sometimes it feels surreal
to me that, you know, this has happened.
It's been a while since it's happened
and I felt like it's the right time to
let you guys know about it. But yeah,
she's uh she's a daughter.
[Music]
But luckily nothing happened to the
back. Thank god nothing happened in the
back. [__] Yo, man. Party in the front,
business in the back. Party in the
front. Business.
[__] man. [__] man. Can't have any
nice things, bro. You can't have any
nice things, bro. This is the third,
bro. I feel like I just said this about
the Corvette that caught fire, bro. Now
the [__] Bugatti, dude. Jesus. What
would you rather have? the rear end of a
Bugatti Pure Sport or the rear end of
the SVJ. I don't know. 100% the Bugatti,
bro. R respectfully, Sugar, you look
beautiful. You look stunning. Stunning,
girl. Look, this this guy can't even get
out.
Bro, he looks like a tarantula getting
out of
What would you rather have, the rear end
of the SVJ or the rear end of the
Bugatti?
Um,
I like the SVJ better. Yeah. You know
that song when Drake said, "I hid the
Bugatti car keys, so you can't drive
it." But you still found it. How
awkward. Or some [__] like that. This is
why [__] Drake hid the car keys from
you. Well, you know what? We learned our
lesson. So, that's definitely not going
to happen here, right? Right. Kind of
testing my luck as a cameraman hanging
out with you, brother. Yeah, you uh
you're like a cat, brother. You're on
your last couple of lives, bro. I can't
even. I already lost count. I could be
on my last one right now potentially.
This doesn't have a roof. This might be
the [__] it right here, bro. The
beauty of it is that this matches
perfectly with my widebody. So, my whole
entire fleet right now is about to be
this Nardo gray vibe. I have a GT3 RS. I
have the lifted truck. I have a another
one. But that's coming very soon. And
it's all going to be Nardo gray. My
whole entire fleet speaking into
manifestation before people decide to
copy me. The normal. So, honestly, one
of the other main reasons why it took me
so long to find an SVJ Roadster is
because of the miles. All these cars
have plus 5,000 mi and they were very
well used or poorly used. Yeah, very
poorly used. This one right here, as you
can see on the dash, it has 994. I got
it with 500 miles. Like, that is unheard
of. I did pay an extra 150 grand for
that, but I know I can beat the living
[__] out of it and it'll be fine or
fineish. He should be able to get in
here. But
look at that. We need
Bro, his head is like halfway out still.
I want be riding like this. Yeah. If I
hit the brakes, there goes his head. You
think this wing could hold me?
It doesn't sound like like you we could
keep doing it. Dude, there's a there's a
dude way bigger than you. Like way
bigger than you. And he stands on this
[__] Like I'm talking about like a
ginormous dude. Ma'am,
do it.
Oh, Lamborghini. Huh? Buckle me. Huh?
Huh? Bugatti. Come on, Bugatti. Come on.
That didn't sound good. That did not
sound good. M again, that does not sound
good.
Yay. He's on his way to take you to
Diddy. All right. So, the cool part
about the frunk is that we can actually
fit the roof in here. So, usually
convertibles they hire by themselves.
This one is manual, which kind of sucks,
but it does fit in here perfectly. I
don't know how to put it on. So, an
interesting fact is that I have never
personally modified a car. This is the
first car I have ever modified. I've
never done exhaust. I've never done
wheels. I've never done anything other
than wrap. Why? Because I just don't
like the downtime of the car being in
the shop for 2, 3 weeks. I just like as
soon as I buy it, I want to drive. But
this one's been down for a month ever
since I bought it. And I did the wheels,
tires, lowering kit, exhaust, tune, all
came out to like $60,000. Everything as
a whole. That's a whole car. That's a
whole C63 right there. It is. But it
made this a whole other car.
That's like the mating car for the SVT.
What is that? I think it's a proper
moment for us to see what this thing
does, right? To see what $60,000 of a
tune exhaust is. Better see like 10 foot
flames on this. If not, you got scammed.
So, I just found this button right here.
This one. Like, bro, there's no way the
back window goes up or down. Look at
this. It's to hear the exhaust more when
you drive. Wow. I had no idea.
[Applause]
[Music]
Nice. That's what I'm [__] talking
about. Oh, I love the downshift.
[Music]
Yo, I don't think the video does it
justice, brother.
[Music]
[__]
Officer. Officer. That was Officer had
us. I could explain. Officer, I just
don't give a [__] The double dead champ
does whatever the [__] he wants. It's a
rental. It's free. It doesn't matter.
That's fantastic. I saw you spit the
fire. You saw fire? Yeah. [__] yeah. It
looks so fun. Yeah. Yeah. So, you're
going to have to get on the car. You're
going to have to come in here right now.
We could trade anytime. Yeah. Anytime.
Hide your girl. Hide your boyfriend. I
mean, uh, h, hide everything cuz I'm
coming. Oh, look who it is. Hello.
I know it's a long story. She has a V12.
You don't. And she's louder. She's
louder. She doesn't have a roof. I know.
We're going to figure out what we do,
you know, sweetie. But until then, I'mma
set and forget in this [__] People
watching this video don't know why
you're bald. Oh, that's right. Damn. The
reason why David is bald is because he
made a bet on week two of the challenge.
Yeah. It was like really really early on
that if he did not hit the goal for the
week, I was going to get a face tattoo.
Yeah. And little did he know that if you
say something to the people I was not
going to get a face tattoo, but bro, but
people take that [__] to heart. Like
people like whatever you say, you have
to back it 100%. And then people were
eating him up because he didn't get the
face tattoo. Obviously, it was a joke.
So the third week if we didn't hit the
goal, he was going to shave his head.
Uhhuh. I mean I was I was I didn't want
to do it cuz I mean I I I really I
really thought we were going to get it
done. But I mean as you guys can see we
did not get it done.
But it's okay. You live and you learn
now. You know whatever you tell the
people you have to do no matter what.
Yeah.
[Music]
Oh, you didn't see the cop? That was
Yeah.
No, but he's cool. Oh, yeah. He's coming
100%. You sure? 100%. Oh, no. Yeah. Now
I saw him. Yeah.
No. No.
You're going to put us over 100%.
[Music]
No, we're
no.
It literally sounds like [__] guns,
bro. We saw the cop and everything, bro.
He got pull over. Yeah, bro. He got
behind us and everything, but he didn't
pull us over. Yeah, he didn't pull us
over. Can he stop you? No. No. And like
I downshifted by accident. Big ass
flame. He didn't pull us over. So, I
actually want to see how big the flames
are. Shall we? Tuck
on a regular [__] Famous lame but they
stay on my dick. New joint is
embarrassing [__] You talk to the cops
on some therapist [__] Yeah. Like you
love this American [__] But really the
truth is you're scared of the six. Yeah.
Scared of the six. Yeah. You're scared
of the six. How you been, bro? Finally
meeting you, bro. It's crazy, brother.
It's crazy. I said I'm going to move to
Miami. I'm going to see Alex one day.
And here we are, bro. Bro, what's up? My
name's Kuba, bro. You gave me so much
inspiration, man. I It took me a little
while to create this. I think it's going
to be a ve very, very special piece for
you. It has a lot of deep meaning in it.
I would love for you to open that up,
man. What is it? A gift? It's a gift,
man. Yeah. I Wait, did you know I was
going to be here or how did you Yes. So,
actually, I've been setting this up for
quite some time. Oh, god. With your
camera, man. Dude, I did this all by
myself. It took me about 2 weeks to hand
paint and then two more weeks to set it
up with him to make sure it's a perfect
time. I didn't want to rush it, bro.
But, dude, yeah, man. You know, you
know, if you're if you know who this
person here is, you know exactly what
this means to him. Look, this is the
same one that I've had in the back for
like 4 years. Four years. So, if you
look on your YouTube video, very first
YouTube video 4 years ago, your very
first YouTube video in the background.
You have that photo. You can find it
here and there recently. But I'm like,
how the hell has nobody made something
like this yet? So, I was going to do a
cartoon, but I found something
realistic. My girl helped me like
Photoshop it and then we created this.
And then obviously, you know, you know,
man, I I appreciate everything you do
for the community. You give, right? I
mean, I don't really got gifts, bro. So,
this is super sick. Yeah. I mean, I
think you deserve it. I know that that
piece is going to mean a lot to you, you
know? So, I'm going to add it next to
where the other one is, bro. I would
love that, man. Seriously. And
congratulations with everything, man.
You're honestly changing a lot of
different people's lives. Just the
inspiration. I mean, an idea and to act
on it, right? I mean, how old are you
now? I'm 24. 24. I'm 24. If you have a
vision, if you're doing good in life,
anyone else can. It's just you have an
idea, you just got to you got to do it.
You got to you got to start today, man.
That's it. I'm going to put it right
here for now, but I'm going to put it
right here. How's the car, dude? This
means more to me than the car, bro.
Really? The reason why I did all this is
because you helped me out. So, I only
have a demo account. I don't have to
show you there, but I've been doing
pretty good on it, though. Yeah. Like,
I've only taken a couple of trades, but
learning through some of your methods or
whatever. I mean, you can see mostly
blue. Mostly blue. But I'm learning,
man. I'm learning. I mean, maybe this is
an audition to be next month's, you
know, Jac, but you never know. That's
crazy.
What's up, man? How are you doing? Yo,
what the [__] is going on here, bro?
That's my student. You got a Ferrari.
I I don't know if you guys know, but I
did a podcast with him in my Bugatti. I
learned a Ferrari, bro. Yeah, I rented
out. I want to have fun. So, I'm here in
Miami. Thanks to him. So, I'm so
grateful because I said it on the video
on the podcast. Go watch it. The
importance of having a mentor in your
life, that's everything that can change
your whole life by 9 today. And I
started dressing like him, too. Look.
You know,
it's slippery. So, look, it's already
slippery. I'll give it a shot. I'll give
it a shot. Go. Three, two, one, go.
140 seconds. 140. Go inside too if you
need. Where am I at? You want to know
for real? I think you should have known.
Hey, one more. One more. One more. Yo,
why you talking? One more. One more. One
more. One more. One more. One more. Hey,
you shouldn't have done those three.
Hey, let's get it. Let's get it. Oh,
you're getting tired. He dead. He dead.
He's getting tired, bro. He [__] up.
Ego stroking him, bro.
Let's go, brother. Two more. Let's go.
Let's get it. Let's get it. Let's get
it.
[Applause]
135. 135. He did good. He did good. $20.
He got scammed, bro. If I give it
another shot, I got it 100%. 100%. You
don't got it, bro. Second time is 20
times harder. If I come back in 30
minutes, your for Yeah. 30 minutes is
different. Yeah. Right now. No. No.
Right now, back to back.
Okay. Before you leave, can you give me
like some advice? Yeah. Some advice with
trading. I need more context. You
psychology? Really? Cuz I'm not going to
lie. Right now, I'm trading funds. Right
now, I got like four accounts. And you
want to go funded. You don't want to go
personal? No, I want to go personal
eventually like after I withdraw my um
you know, my payouts and stuff. 50% into
live accounts. I mean what like you lose
a lot or you just get wicked out. I get
greedy sometimes. Like I know I'm I'm
good at trading. Like my main problem is
like I kind of get greedy. I get like an
ego. I don't know how to battle it
sometimes. I mean brother what I do just
limit yourself. Like the max you could
take is one or two trades a week.
Anything after that you got to hold
yourself accountable. I mean like like
what I would do like I like eating
chocolates and [__] and if I don't meet
my training plan I can't eat chocolate.
You if you break your training plan you
should cut a dread.
[Music]
That's a good way. It's a good way to
train that trading plan. You never break
your trading plan ever again. Trust
grinding, bro. Good luck, boys.
This is what I needed to go complete the
minute 40 challenge. You'll see.
All right. Three, two, one.
I got a shitty ass.
Oh, it's music and everything.
[Music]
I'm already I'm already cooked.
Almost at 45. Another 45. Almost at 45.
No, bro. Give it a shot. Give it a shot.
Let's see it.
[Music]
Everything
advice for me if I want to start
something like you business, bro. You
got to just [__] figure out exactly
what you want to do and then just give
it 100%. I I have to love what I uh what
I do. Oh, I mean, brother. Yeah. If I
don't love it's not going to work. No, I
mean, bro, I'll be like three nights in
a row where I sleep two hours and I do
it because I love it. What's up, man?
We're from Spain. Back then in 2023.
Congrats on the chat. Thank you,
brother. Appreciate it. Back then in
2023, I was in a trade there where I
made 100 bucks. As of today, May was my
biggest month. 192,000. Holy [__] So,
don't forget, baby. Life changed
quickly. Nice to meet you, man.
Congrats. We're happy for you, bro. Keep
killing it. To be thankful for the
haters because they've been roasting
you. And now look at you. I know, bro.
They call me mad, bro. Jack as [__] Not
going to lie. I love the Joe is square
as [__] I like that. Real recognize
real. You know that's what I'm talking
about. I don't want to interrupt no
more. Have a good night. Nice to meet
you, man. Have fun. God bless. But we
take one quick pick. So crazy night here
in purple. I can't I can't even say like
the feeling of just meeting other like
cool people in person, you know. I love
it. I saw you just got the Bugatti, bro.
Appreciate it, bro. Thank you, bro.
Appreciate it. Love it. Love it.
Bugatti. It's better than the Bugatti.
Yeah. Give him one advice. You guys want
one advice? Yeah. We are only above the
brake cravings season. Like we are
profitable already after 4 years. Yeah.
Okay. What's your biggest issue in
psychology? You're overtrading or you're
undertrading? I don't overtrade anymore.
I for me to give you a good answer, I
understand more of you guys, context.
Yeah, you need some context. So, what is
your biggest issue in psychology?
Oh, so you guys don't believe that that
the money could be real. Exactly.
lot.
Yeah. I mean, bro, you guys already at
the profitable point, bro. You know,
like I trade 0.5. I don't trade one or
2%. What do you think about it? I
perfect. Yeah. I mean, yeah. I mean, I
feel comfortable with that. Yeah. If
you're That's the most important thing.
If I trade with 0.5, I feel like a
[__] I got to bump that [__] up. But
if you feel comfortable with 0.5, but I
don't mean I'll power, too. I won't
regret not saying hi to you, bro. What's
up? Big fan, bro. No, of course, bro.
Pleasure. Pleasure. Hey, awesome, bro.
Thank you, man. Thank you. He g me a lot
of confidence to trade like a 0.5. Like,
I don't feel anything. For sure. I mean,
bro, I would literally not try and
overthink it. Like, if those are the
That's the amount you're okay with
losing. That's the amount you're okay
with losing. And if you're scared of
losing profits. Uh-huh. That's my That's
my issue. Like when it goes always I
close like two pips before TP. I just
cannot. You got to set and forget, bro.
You got to set and forget. That's the
best thing I can say. Yeah. Just set and
forget. Or when you don't set and
forget, you got to hold yourself
accountable. Basically, like something
that What's something that you like a
lot? Uh that joint. Your joint. Okay.
Whenever you don't set and forget, you
can't smoke your joint. Okay. So every
single time Yeah. You have to punish
yourself. So every single time you don't
sudden forget, you're like, "Fuck, I
can't smoke my joint." You know, that's
going to suck. And it might not seem as
deep as it is, but it goes really deep.
Believe me. Trust me.
Something that small can completely
change everything.
All right. Thank you, brother. Guys,
pleasure.
All I care about is money that I'm sip
it. I'mma smoke it till it's done. I
don't really give a [__] my excuses
that I'm young and I'm only getting
older. Somebody should have told you I'm
[Music]
could be depending on how you sh
Heat.